Guide to the Barry Gifford Papers M0927
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 8. Accession 2013-023: Manuscripts for 9 Books
  - The Stars Above Veracruz: corrections (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Stars Above Veracruz: corrections (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Stars Above Veracruz (Box 2, Folders 2-4)
  - The Imagination of the Heart (Box 2, Folders 5-10)
  - Sad Stories of the Death of Kings: Original Typescript (Box 3, Folders 1-2)
  - Sad Stories of the Death of Kings: copy (Box 3, Folders 3-4)
  - Sad Stories of the Death of Kings (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Sad Stories Proofs (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sad Stories of the Death of Kings (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Drawings for Sad Stories of the Death of Kings (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sad Stories of the Death of Kings (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Las Cuatro Reinas (The four Queens) (Box 3, Folders 10-11)
  - Las Cuatro Reinas (The four Queens) Poems (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Port Tropique Galley Proofs Dec. 2008 for 7 stories edition (Box 4, Folders 2-3)
  - The Roy Stories (Box 4, Folders 4-7)
  - The Roy Stories (Box 4, Folders 8-12)
  - The Roy Stories (Box 4, Folders 13-14)
  - Original Typescript Memories from a Sinking Ship (Box 5, Folders 1-2)
  - Contract for Memories from a Sinking Ship (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Memories from a Sinking Ship (Box 5, Folders 4-7)
  - Memories from a Sinking Ship Material (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cover of Imaging Paradise (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Imaging Paradise: New and Selected Poems, Typescript (Box 5, Folders 10-13)
  - Imaging Paradise: New and Selected Poems, Manuscript (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Imaging Paradise: New and Selected Poems, Manuscript (Box 6, Folders 1-2)
  - Imaging Paradise: corrected galley proofs (Box 6, Folders 3-6)
  - Reversion of Rights to the Cavalry Charges (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Cavalry Charges (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Cavalry Charges: manuscript (Box 6, Folders 9-11)
  - The Cavalry Charges: manuscript (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - The Cavalry Charges: manuscript (Box 7, Folders 1-2)
  - The Cavalry Charges material (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Madrugada: manuscript (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Various Manuscripts (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Seven Stories Press (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Notebook (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Newsclipping (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Notebook (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Series 9. Accession 2016-017